AVINASH

ADI's North Lake View Apartment, Agrahara Village, Yelahanka Bangalore -560 064. Contact: +91-7406840685

avipolicepatil@gmail.com

Career Objective

To work in a challenging and creative environment to expose my innovative skills with reliable people who provide me a scope to improve my career and effectively contribute towards the goals of the organization.

Summary

2.3 years' experience in Civil Engineering with focus on Project and Construction Management, Quality Management System, Operation & Field Engineering including HSE System and Quantity surveying. Experienced in onshore facilities encompassing structural platforms, high-rise residential, and commercial buildings.

Employment Experience

1.	Apr 2021 - Till Date	Salarpuria Sattva Group Building 3, 4 th floor, Salarpruria Windsor, Halsoor Road, Bangalore-560042.	Site Engineer
2.	May 2019 –Mar 2021	New Consolidated Construction Company Ltd 5th floor, Ranka Chambers, Cunningham Rd, Vasanth Nagar, Bengaluru, Karnataka 560052	QA/QC Engineer

Projects

1 Salarpuria Sattva Group

Project: Salarpuria Sattva Exotic (Apr 2021 to till date)

Salarpuria Sattva Exotic is a 6 Acre campus located in Bagaluru, Bangalore, with 3 Towers of 350 flats and a Club House.

- Analysis of Project Plans, Plumb Alignment&Levels.
- Assisting the Manager to reach a viable solution to the issues that would crop up during the process of execution.
- Monitoring quality control and health and safety matters onsite.
- > Guide the contractor, staff about better construction practices on a daily basis for the betterment of the project, progress quality and safety.
- ➤ Issuing Non-Confirmative Action Reports NCR 's for the quality issues found in prior & post checking, leading to immediaterectifications.
- Analyzing the measurements, and valuation of works (on site & from drawing)

2 New Consolidated Construction Company Ltd.

Project: Prestige Tech Cloud – Tech Park – 7 Towers – 2B+G+8 floors (May 2019 to Mar 2021)

- > Planning, organizing numerous test of materials from beginning of the project.
- ➤ Coordinating with client and subcontractor regarding schedules and monitoring the quality of project, milestones and consistently achieving quality and schedule.
- Review engineering drawings and specifications and ensure the correctness of transfer from drawing details to the ground as per quality standards.
- Preparation of final jobs close out report and analyzing with theoretical qualities as built up drawings.
- Monitoring all the ITP and MAR reports and timely conducting on site Tests.

Education

•	B.E	-	Civil Eng. (2019) with 7.8 CGPA at NCET	-Bangalore
•	Schooling	-	PUC (2015) with 81.5 % at Mahesh PU college	- Mangalore
			S.S.L.C (2012) with 86.24% at Vidyaranya High School	- Bidar

Strengths

- Confident, determined, and a teamplayer.
- Ability to cope up with different situations.
- Active listener and a quicklearner.
- SmartWorker
- Innovative

Software Skills

Civil Software : AutoCAD , STAAD
 Software : MS Office, MS Program

Personal Data

Father's Name : Basavaraj Patil
Date of Birth :11/11/1996
Mother Tongue :Kannada
Marital Status :Unmarried

• Languages Know : Kannada, Hindi, Telugu & English.

• Permanent address : Adi's North lake View Apts Agrahara Village Bangalore 50064

Declaration

I hereby declare that the above information given by me is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Place:Bangalore Yours faithfully

Date: